(DNA identification regarding the relationship between Xu Xixi and Sample B)
(تحديد الحمض النووي فيما يتعلق بالعلاقة بين Xu Xixi والعينة B)
(The possibility of being twins is 99.9999%) Twins?
(احتمالية أن تكون توأماً هي 99.9999٪) توائم؟
Why have I never heard my dad mention it before?
لماذا لم أسمع والدي يذكرها من قبل؟
I just found out too.
أنا فقط اكتشفت ذلك أيضا.
Seems like An Yemi has hidden quite a lot from me.
يبدو أن Yemi قد أخفت الكثير عني.
Sorry.
آسف.
What are you apologizing for?
ما الذي تعتذر عنه؟
I don't care at all
أنا لا أهتم على الإطلاق
about what she plans behind my back.
حول ما تخطط وراء ظهري.
As you can see,
كما ترون،
I wanted to stay here by myself.
كنت أرغب في البقاء هنا لوحدي.
Here,
هنا،
I can go wherever I want
يمكنني الذهاب حيثما أريد
without reporting to anyone.
دون إبلاغ أي شخص.
And no one would be
ولن يكون هناك أحد
monitoring me 24/7.
مراقبة لي 24/7.
Plus, no one would be
بالإضافة إلى ذلك ، لن يكون هناك أحد
serving me every day
تخدمني كل يوم
while being afraid of not pleasing me.
بينما كنت خائفًا من عدم إرضائي.
I don't have much time left.
ليس لدي الكثير من الوقت.
I just want to live happily.
أنا فقط أريد أن أعيش بسعادة.
So
لذا
I won't leave with you guys.
لن أغادر معكم يا رفاق.
Lu Jinyan.
لو جينيان.
If it weren't for this crisis,
لولا هذه الأزمة ،
you wouldn't have come to find me.
ما كنت لتجد لي.
Ms. Xu.
السيدة شو.
This is your crisis too.
هذه هي أزمتك أيضا.
Do you remember Dr. Zheng?
هل تتذكر الدكتور زينج؟
His team will be returning from overseas tomorrow
فريقه سيعود من الخارج غدا
for a comprehensive medical checkup for you.
لإجراء فحص طبي شامل لك.
If An Yue is in charge of the checkup,
إذا كان An Yue مسؤولاً عن الفحص ،
her identity would definitely be exposed.
سيتم الكشف عن هويتها بالتأكيد.
Till then,
حتى ذلك الحين،
do you think you can still hide here?
هل تعتقد أنه لا يزال بإمكانك الاختباء هنا؟
Don't you miss your dad?
ألا تشتاق لوالدك؟
He has been working hard and worrying about your illness.
لقد كان يعمل بجد ويقلق بشأن مرضك.
Don't you want to meet him?
الا تريدين مقابلته
It's late.
إنه متأخر.
Let's talk about it tomorrow.
دعنا نتحدث عن ذلك غدا.
=Love of Replica=
= حب النسخة المتماثلة =
=Episode 10=
= الحلقة 10 =
Looks so alike.
تبدو متشابهة جدًا.
No wonder even my dad couldn't recognize you.
لا عجب حتى والدي لم يستطع التعرف عليك.
It's really not plastic surgery.
إنها في الحقيقة ليست جراحة تجميلية.
I guarantee I've never done it.
أنا أضمن أنني لم أفعل ذلك أبدًا.
So,
لذا،
are we really twins?
هل نحن حقا توأم؟
From the perspective of paternity testing,
من منظور اختبار الأبوة ،
there are 99.99% possibilities that
هناك احتمالات بنسبة 99.99٪
we are twins.
نحن توأم.
If we are twins,
إذا كنا توأمان ،
are all of our organs exactly the same?
هل جميع أعضائنا متطابقة تمامًا؟
I wonder.
انا اتعجب.
Okay.
تمام.
As long as Xu Yongyu leaves the house,
طالما غادر Xu Yongyu المنزل ،
the system will alert us immediately.
سيقوم النظام بتنبيهنا على الفور.
So this will ensure no element of surprise.
لذلك لن يضمن هذا عنصر المفاجأة.
I wonder what's
أتساءل ما هو
going on at An Yue's side.
يجري في جانب An Yue.
We've located her.
لقد حددنا موقعها.
We're going back now.
سنعود الآن.
I can go back with you
يمكنني العودة معك
but
لكن
on one condition.
بشرط واحد.
Sir,
سيد،
Dr. Zheng will arrive at the airport in two hours
سيصل الدكتور تشنغ إلى المطار في غضون ساعتين
and he will arrive at the hospital at 7 p.m. sharp.
وسيصل إلى المستشفى الساعة السابعة مساءً.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
I'll go see Xixi first.
سأذهب وأرى Xixi أولاً.
Xu Yongyu has departed.
غادر شو يونغ يو.
(56 more minutes until they reach the destination)
(56 دقيقة أخرى حتى تصل إلى الوجهة)
Jinyan, urgent!
جنيان ، عاجل!
(Xu Yongyu has started off early.)
(بدأ Xu Yongyu مبكراً).
(How much longer do you need?)
(كم من الوقت تحتاج؟)
Probably another hour.
ربما ساعة أخرى.
Xu Yongyu is here.
شو يونغ يو هنا.
You guys go ahead.
انطلقوا يا رفاق.
Let me handle him.
دعني أتعامل معه.
He's a suspicious person.
إنه شخص مشبوه.
If we stop him from going upstairs forcefully,
إذا منعناه من الصعود بقوة ،
he'll only become more suspicious.
سيصبح أكثر ريبة.
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
I won't stop him that way.
لن أوقفه بهذه الطريقة.
Come.
يأتي.
Mr. Xu is here.
السيد شو هنا.
Why are you here?
لماذا أنت هنا؟
Xixi asked me to come and keep her company.
طلبت مني Xixi الحضور والاحتفاظ برفقتها.
Where is Xixi then?
أين Xixi إذن؟
Xixi.
يتبول.
Mr. Xu.
السيد شو.
Xixi could be a little nervous
يمكن أن يكون Xixi متوترًا بعض الشيء
today because of the examination.
اليوم بسبب الفحص.
She didn't sleep well last night
لم تنم جيدًا الليلة الماضية
so she's still resting.
لذلك هي لا تزال تستريح.
Well, let's not disturb her rest then.
حسنًا ، دعنا لا نزعج راحتها بعد ذلك.
Zhou.
تشو.
How was the airport pick-up?
كيف كان النقل من المطار؟
Let me check.
دعني أتحقق.
The flight is expected to land in one hour.
من المتوقع أن تهبط الرحلة خلال ساعة واحدة.
We should wake her up early
يجب أن نوقظها مبكرا
so she doesn't wake up grumpy
حتى لا تستيقظ غاضبة
and then refuses to cooperate with the examination.
ثم يرفض التعاون مع الفحص.
Mr. Xu, let me handle it.
سيد (شو) ، دعني أتعامل مع الأمر.
You may rest first.
يمكنك الراحة أولا.
Ding Beifan.
دينغ بيفان.
Jiang Tiancheng.
جيانغ تيانشينغ.
(Where have you all been?)
(أين كنتم جميعا؟)
Where's Xixi?
أين Xixi؟
Is she awake?
هل هي مستيقظة؟
Yes, she is.
نعم هي.
She was very grumpy when being woken up just now.
كانت غاضبة للغاية عندما استيقظت للتو.
Mr. Xu.
السيد شو.
Where's Xixi?
أين Xixi؟
Where is she?
أين هي؟
And also Lu Jinyan?
وكذلك لو جنيان؟
Why isn't he around as well?
لماذا لا يتواجد كذلك؟
Xixi is taking a shower.
Xixi يستحم.
I don't know about Lu Jinyan.
لا أعرف عن لو جينيان.
Maybe Xixi got him to go buy something.
ربما جعله Xixi يذهب لشراء شيء ما.
Lies.
يكذب.
All of you
كلكم
were helping Xixi to avoid the checkup
كانوا يساعدون Xixi على تجنب الفحص
by lying to me.
بالكذب علي.
Mr. Xu.
السيد شو.
Xixi.
يتبول.
What's going on, old man?
ما الذي يحدث أيها الرجل العجوز؟
Didn't you see that I was showering?
ألم ترى أنني كنت أستحم؟
Sorry, Xixi.
آسف ، Xixi.
I'm just worried about you.
انا فقط قلق عليك.
(An Yue)
(أن يو)
We would know if I'm okay
سنعرف ما إذا كنت بخير
after the checkup.
بعد الفحص.
Glad you're okay.
سعيد لأنك بخير.
You scared me there.
لقد أخفتني هناك.
This thing was indeed
كان هذا الشيء بالفعل
quite good.
جيد نوعا ما.
It sounds very realistic in there.
يبدو واقعيا جدا هناك.
Luckily, you're smart.
لحسن الحظ ، أنت ذكي.
It's not because I'm smart.
ليس لأنني ذكي.
But I understand Tian Sui's personality better.
لكني أفهم شخصية تيان سوي بشكل أفضل.
Once she told a lie,
بمجرد أن كذبت ،
she would do everything to make it come true.
كانت ستفعل كل ما في وسعها لتحقيق ذلك.
Give me back my pants.
أعد لي سروالي.
Dr. Zheng has arrived at the airport.
وصل الدكتور تشنغ إلى المطار.
Now off to the hospital.
الآن انتقل إلى المستشفى.
Old man.
رجل عجوز.
Xixi, dry your hair quickly.
Xixi ، جفف شعرك بسرعة.
It's time to go.
حان وقت الذهاب.
Old man, I miss you so much.
أيها الرجل العجوز ، أفتقدك كثيراً.
Xixi, my baby.
Xixi ، طفلي.
When did you start acting coquettishly?
متى بدأت تتصرف بغنج؟
As long as you
طالما انك
take good care of your body.
اعتني بجسمك جيدًا.
Dad
أب
will be happier than ever.
سيكون أسعد من أي وقت مضى.
The fishing village is not safe.
قرية الصيد ليست آمنة.
You can stay with me for the time being.
يمكنك البقاء معي في الوقت الحاضر.
You've been staying in a hotel, right?
كنت تقيم في فندق ، أليس كذلك؟
Yes.
نعم.
So that Xu Yongyu won't find out about my true identity.
حتى لا يكتشف Xu Yongyu هويتي الحقيقية.
Can I take a look around?
هل يمكنني إلقاء نظرة حولنا؟
My girlfriend.
صديقتي الحميمة.
Feel free.
خذ راحتك.
Let me help you.
دعني اساعدك.
Okay.
تمام.
When did you buy these?
متى اشتريت هذه؟
These are prepared by Tian Sui for you.
تم إعداد هذه بواسطة Tian Sui من أجلك.
She was worried that you didn't have clean clothes.
كانت قلقة من عدم وجود ملابس نظيفة.
So she prepared some clothes for you in advance,
لذا جهزت لك بعض الملابس مقدمًا ،
as well as toiletries.
وكذلك أدوات النظافة.
Tian Sui is a person who speaks her mind but she has a soft heart.
تيان سوي شخص يتحدث عن رأيها لكن قلبها رقيق.
She may not be easy to approach,
قد لا يكون من السهل الاقتراب منها ،
but she's actually very thoughtful.
لكنها في الواقع مدروسة للغاية.
(Oil Soap)
(صابون زيت)
(Family planning products)
(منتجات تنظيم الأسرة)
What's so funny?
ما المضحك في ذلك؟
Nothing,
لا شئ،
I was just thinking
انا فقط كنت افكر
that you're right.
أنك على حق.
She's quite thoughtful.
إنها مدروسة للغاية.
I'm going to wash up.
سوف اغتسل.
Well...
حسنًا...
Goodnight.
طاب مساؤك.
I'll sleep on the couch.
سأنام على الأريكة.
Well...
حسنًا...
Goodnight.
طاب مساؤك.
♪I want to watch you every moment♪
♪ اريد ان اشاهدك كل لحظة ♪
♪How about you♪
♪ ماذا عنك ♪
♪Is this a dream♪
♪ هل هذا حلم ♪
I'll help you with the blanket.
سأساعدك في البطانية.
♪Except for my heartbeat, the world is silent♪
باستثناء دقات قلبي ، العالم صامت
♪My gaze pauses, my breath stops♪
♪ توقفت نظري ، توقف أنفاسي ♪
♪My heart♪
♪ قلبي ♪
♪My love♪
♪ حبي
♪I hope for life♪
♪ اتمنى الحياة ♪
♪hold you tight every moment♪
♪ تمسك بك بقوة في كل لحظة
♪Like in the vast universe, never drying up♪
♪ كما هو الحال في الكون الواسع ، لا يجف أبدًا
♪My heart♪
♪ قلبي ♪
♪My love♪
♪ حبي
♪I hope you feel my love♪
♪ أتمنى أن تشعر بحبي ♪
♪Only you in my eyes♪
أنت فقط في عيني ♪
♪Love you♪
♪ أحبك ♪
♪I want to watch you every moment♪
♪ اريد ان اشاهدك كل لحظة ♪
♪How about you♪
♪ ماذا عنك ♪
♪Is this a dream♪
♪ هل هذا حلم ♪
♪Except for my heartbeat, the world is silent♪
باستثناء دقات قلبي ، العالم صامت
Lu Jinyan.
لو جينيان.
I forgot that I came on my period.
لقد نسيت أنني أتيت في دورتي الشهرية.
I'll make you some brown sugar drinks.
سأعد لك بعض مشروبات السكر البني.
The brain tumor lesion
آفة ورم المخ
hasn't shown any obvious signs of deterioration,
لم تظهر أي علامات واضحة على التدهور ،
but other physical indicators are not optimistic.
لكن المؤشرات المادية الأخرى ليست متفائلة.
What's the matter with you?
ما خطبك؟
I just feel like
أنا فقط أشعر
she's changed a lot recently.
لقد تغيرت كثيرًا مؤخرًا.
It's nothing.
لا شئ.
I'm just overthinking.
أنا فقط أفكر.
Since she is seriously ill now,
بما أنها مريضة الآن ،
it's better to be safe
من الأفضل أن تكون آمنًا
and change the checkup back to once a week.
وتغيير الفحص مرة أخرى إلى مرة واحدة في الأسبوع.
Understood.
مفهوم.
However,
لكن،
regardless of whether there are any clues
بغض النظر عما إذا كانت هناك أية أدلة
left by An Yemi about the child,
تركته آن يمي عن الطفل ،
we can't delay Ms. Xu's surgery any longer.
لا يمكننا تأخير جراحة السيدة زو أكثر من ذلك.
If, as you said,
إذا ، كما قلت ،
that child is still alive,
هذا الطفل لا يزال على قيد الحياة ،
we need to find her as soon as possible.
نحن بحاجة للعثور عليها في أقرب وقت ممكن.
I know.
أنا أعرف.
I will hurry up.
سوف اسرع.
Ms. Xu.
السيدة شو.
Get out, stop following me.
اخرج ، توقف عن ملاحقتي.
I'm sorry, Miss.
أنا آسف يا آنسة.
These are all Mr. Xu's orders.
هذه كلها أوامر السيد شو.
Do you think there's any difference between how
هل تعتقد أن هناك فرقًا بين الكيفية
Lu Jinyan treated me before and after the car accident?
لو جنيان عالجني قبل وبعد حادث السيارة؟
I think whether it was before
أعتقد ما إذا كان ذلك من قبل
or after the car accident,
أو بعد حادث السيارة ،
Lu has always been absolutely responsible for you.
لطالما كان لو مسؤولاً تمامًا عنك.
He is the benchmark for our learning.
إنه المعيار لتعلمنا.
It's just that
إنه فقط كذلك
Lu would be more popular now than before.
سيكون لو أكثر شعبية الآن من ذي قبل.
Even netizens say that
حتى مستخدمي الإنترنت يقولون ذلك
Lu is a textbook of the bodyguard industry.
لو هو كتاب مدرسي لصناعة الحراس الشخصيين.
What does that mean?
ماذا يعني ذالك؟
(Xu Xixi VS Handsome Bodyguard)
(Xu Xixi VS وسيم حارس شخصي)
You're awake.
انت مستيقظ.
Breakfast is ready.
الفطور جاهز.
You can have it when you get up.
يمكنك الحصول عليه عندما تستيقظ.
I'll go to Xu's house later.
سأذهب إلى منزل Xu لاحقًا.
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
I'll behave and not reveal my identity while staying at home.
سأتصرف ولن أفصح عن هويتي أثناء إقامتي في المنزل.
Once we find out the truth,
بمجرد اكتشاف الحقيقة ،
we will bring those who harmed my dad to justice.
سوف نقدم أولئك الذين أساءوا والدي إلى العدالة.
Then we'll leave this place and live the life we want.
ثم سنغادر هذا المكان ونعيش الحياة التي نريدها.
(We need to discuss what to do next.)
(نحتاج إلى مناقشة ما يجب فعله بعد ذلك).
(Ask An Yue to wait for me at the company.)
(اطلب من An Yue أن تنتظرني في الشركة.)
(I want to see her.)
(اريد رؤيتها.)
She wants to see you.
هي تريد رؤيتك.
Who made you angry
من جعلك تغضب
so early in the morning?
في وقت مبكر جدا في الصباح؟
Since when I'm happy after a physical examination?
منذ متى أنا سعيد بعد الفحص البدني؟
Hey, Xixi.
مرحبًا ، Xixi.
Let me tell you.
دعني أخبرك.
I'm fine.
أنا بخير.
If you're not tired of saying these, I am tired of hearing them.
إذا لم تتعب من قول ذلك ، فقد سئمت من سماعها.
If you really want to make me happy,
إذا كنت تريد حقًا أن تجعلني سعيدًا ،
just promise me one thing.
فقط أوعدني بشيء واحد.
What is it?
ما هذا؟
I want to give Lu Jinyan a break.
أريد أن أعطي لو جينيان استراحة.
He's been with me all these days.
لقد كان معي كل هذه الأيام.
It's too hard on him.
من الصعب جدا عليه.
I want him to rest.
اريده ان يرتاح
Okay.
تمام.
But you have to promise me
لكن عليك أن تعدني
to go for check-ups every week from now on.
للذهاب لإجراء الفحوصات كل أسبوع من الآن فصاعدًا.
Okay.
تمام.
But I don't want to affect my work.
لكني لا أريد أن أؤثر على عملي.
Well...
حسنًا...
This is too hard.
هذا صعب جدا.
Your body can't handle it.
لا يستطيع جسمك التعامل معها.
It's nothing.
لا شئ.
I'm bored staying at home.
أشعر بالملل من البقاء في المنزل.
No worries.
لا شكر على واجب.
I won't let work affect my health.
لن أترك العمل يؤثر على صحتي.
Okay.
تمام.
From now on,
من الان فصاعدا،
you have to get my permission
عليك الحصول على إذن مني
for all your whereabouts
لجميع أماكن وجودك
and schedule.
والجدول الزمني.
Good girl.
فتاة جيدة.
Good morning, Mr. Xu.
صباح الخير سيد شو.
Ms. Xu, the car is ready.
السيدة شو ، السيارة جاهزة.
Old man, I'm going to the company.
الرجل العجوز ، أنا ذاهب إلى الشركة.
Don't you forget
لا تنسى
what you promised me earlier.
ما وعدتني به في وقت سابق.
I've forgotten about your conditioned reflex.
لقد نسيت أمر رد الفعل الشرطي الخاص بك.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
Xu Xixi insisted on meeting at the company,
أصر Xu Xixi على الاجتماع في الشركة ،
but I didn't expect
لكني لم أتوقع
that you're so good at disguising yourself.
أنك بارع في التنكر.
I didn't recognize you at first glance.
لم أتعرف عليك للوهلة الأولى.
That's fine.
هذا جيّد.
How was last night's experience?
كيف كانت تجربة الليلة الماضية؟
What experience?
ما التجربة؟
Really?
حقًا؟
Lu Jinyan,
لو جينيان ،
strong on the outside, but weak on the inside.
قوي من الخارج ، لكنه ضعيف من الداخل.
So those family planning products were bought by you?
هل تم شراء منتجات تنظيم الأسرة هذه بواسطتك؟
Of course.
بالطبع.
I secretly put them in there
وضعتهم هناك سرا
under Ding Beifan's nose.
تحت أنف دينغ بيفان.
Otherwise, who do you think bought them, Ding Beifan?
خلاف ذلك ، من باعتقادك اشتراها ، دينغ بيفان؟
He would even object to
حتى أنه سيعترض على
you going to Lu Jinyan's house.
أنت ذاهب إلى منزل لو جينيان.
So,
لذا،
did you end up using them?
هل انتهيت من استخدامها؟
How many
كم عدد
did you use?
هل استخدمت؟
You guys seem to be having a good chat.
يبدو أنكم تجريون محادثة جيدة يا رفاق.
We're discussing what things need to
نحن نناقش ما تحتاجه الأشياء
be handed over to you.
يتم تسليمها لك.
So that you can be yourself again.
حتى تتمكن من أن تكون على طبيعتك مرة أخرى.
It also allowed An Yue to exit smoothly.
كما سمح لـ An Yue بالخروج بسلاسة.
Since we're all here,
نظرًا لأننا جميعًا هنا ،
let's make sure we're on the same page.
لنتأكد من أننا في نفس الصفحة.
So that we don't make any mistakes in public in the future.
حتى لا نرتكب أي أخطاء في العلن في المستقبل.
Don't bother.
لا تهتم.
As long as I share Xu Xixi's identity with her,
طالما أشاركها هوية Xu Xixi ،
she'll be responsible for socializing and liaising.
ستكون مسؤولة عن التواصل الاجتماعي والاتصال.
I'll be responsible for the routine checks every week.
سأكون مسؤولاً عن الفحوصات الروتينية كل أسبوع.
Isn't everything resolved then?
ألا يتم حل كل شيء بعد ذلك؟
♪I'm in the darkness all by myself♪
♪ أنا في الظلام بمفردي
♪Trying to look for you Wherever you are♪
♪ تحاول البحث عنك أينما كنت ♪
♪Did you know? I'm standing on this empty road, don’t know where to go♪
♪ هل تعلم؟  أنا أقف على هذا الطريق الخالي ، لا أعرف إلى أين أذهب
♪I'm calling your name♪
♪ انا ادعو اسمك ♪
♪If I had a chance to do this over again♪
♪ إذا سنحت لي الفرصة للقيام بذلك مرة أخرى
♪I know for sure it wouldn't be the same♪
♪ أعرف على وجه اليقين أنه لن يكون هو نفسه ♪
♪I can't stop loving you♪
♪ لا أستطيع التوقف عن حبك ♪
♪I can't stop love for you♪
♪ لا أستطيع التوقف عن الحب من أجلك ♪
♪My heart is saying it is very true♪
♪ قلبي يقول هذا صحيح جدا ♪
♪I can't stop loving you♪
♪ لا أستطيع التوقف عن حبك ♪
♪I can't stop love for you♪
♪ لا أستطيع التوقف عن الحب من أجلك ♪
♪Even though I know that you don't feel the same♪
♪ على الرغم من أنني أعلم أنك لا تشعر بنفس الشعور ♪
♪I can't stop loving you♪
♪ لا أستطيع التوقف عن حبك ♪
♪I can't stop love for you♪
♪ لا أستطيع التوقف عن الحب من أجلك ♪
♪My heart is saying it is very true♪
♪ قلبي يقول هذا صحيح جدا ♪
♪I can't stop loving you♪
♪ لا أستطيع التوقف عن حبك ♪
♪I can't stop love for you♪
♪ لا أستطيع التوقف عن الحب من أجلك ♪
♪Even though I know that you don't feel the same♪
♪ على الرغم من أنني أعلم أنك لا تشعر بنفس الشعور ♪
♪I'll let you go♪
♪ سأدعك تذهب ♪
♪I can't stop loving you♪
♪ لا أستطيع التوقف عن حبك ♪
♪I can't stop love for you♪
♪ لا أستطيع التوقف عن الحب من أجلك ♪
♪My heart is saying it is very true♪
♪ قلبي يقول هذا صحيح جدا ♪
♪I can't stop loving you♪
♪ لا أستطيع التوقف عن حبك ♪
♪I can't stop love for you♪
♪ لا أستطيع التوقف عن الحب من أجلك ♪
♪Even though I know that you don't feel the same♪
♪ على الرغم من أنني أعلم أنك لا تشعر بنفس الشعور ♪
♪I'll let you go♪
♪ سأدعك تذهب ♪